Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 7) [labeled on canister as Offense 1 of 2], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 7) [labeled on canister as Offense 2 of 2], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 7) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as Defense 1 of 2], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2], 27 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 8 Nov. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 8 Nov. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 8 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 8 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 1 Nov. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
  This film has been converted to digital beta (also stored in carton 24), and is also stored as an mp4 file from which copies can be reproduced
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State Junior Varsity vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Junior Varsity (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 1], 17 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State Junior Varsity vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Junior Varsity (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 2], 17 Oct. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 13 Sept. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. West Virginia (Peach Bowl) (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 31 Dec. 1975 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. West Virginia (Peach Bowl) (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 31 Dec. 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; color; sound
- NC State vs. West Virginia (Peach Bowl) (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 31 Dec. 1975 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. West Virginia (Peach Bowl) (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 31 Dec. 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey, Don Buckey (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as #1] (copy 1), 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 50 seconds; color; no sound
- NCSU 1975 Peach Bowl Film (general campus scenes), 16 December 1975 (Carton 25)
  AV11.FM.5
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey, Don Buckey (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as #1] (copy 2), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Narrative of Dave Buckey/Don Buckey highlight film #1, 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as #2] (copy 1), 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 52 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as #2] (copy 2), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Narrative of Dave Buckey highlight film #2, 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as #3] (copy 1), 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 35 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as #3] (copy 2), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as #3] (copy 3), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as #3] (copy 4), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Dave Buckey (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as #3] (copy 5), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Narrative of Dave Buckey highlight film #3, 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Tom Higgins (copy 1), 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 37 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Tom Higgins (copy 2), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Narrative of Tom Higgins highlight film, 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Eddie Poole (copy 1), 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 56 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Eddie Poole (copy 2), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Eddie Poole (copy 3), 1975 (Carton 25)
- Narrative of Eddie Poole highlight film, 1975 (Carton 25)
- Player highlights: Bruce Shaw (1 of 2) [labeled on film as 51.8], 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 8 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Bruce Shaw (2 of 2) [labeled on film as 51.9], 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 10 seconds; color; no sound
- Player highlights: Charley Young, 1975 (Carton 25)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 13 seconds; color, no sound
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 23 Oct. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (copy 1), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (copy 2), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (copy 1), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (copy 2), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 13 Nov. 1976 (Carton 25)
- NC State vs. Furman (1 of 5) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 4 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Furman (2 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 4 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Furman (3 of 5) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 4 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Furman (4 of 5) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 4 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Furman (5 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 4 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Indiana (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 2 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Indiana (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 2 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as Offense what's left], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense and Kicking], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 9 Oct. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 25 Sept. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 26)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense and Kicking], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; sound
- NC State vs. Penn State (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Nov. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; black white; sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 30 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 30 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 30 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 30 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
  This film has been converted to digital beta (stored in carton 24), and is also stored as an mp4 file from which copies can be reproduced
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 12 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 16 Oct. 1976 (Carton 27)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter & Kicking], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 9 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 11 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 9 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 11 Sept. 1976 (Carton 28)
- Atlantic Coast Conference pre-season highlights, 1976 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 25 minutes; color; sound
- Miscellaneous football footage (1 of 5) [labeled on canister as 20-21], 1976 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 15 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- Miscellaneous football footage (2 of 5) [labeled on canister as 32-33], 1976 (Carton 28)
- Miscellaneous football footage (3 of 5) [labeled on canister as 34-35], 1976 (Carton 28)
- Miscellaneous football footage (4 of 5) [labeled on canister as 48-49], 1976 (Carton 28)
- Miscellaneous football footage (5 of 5) [labeled on canister as 72-73], 1976 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 12 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Auburn (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
  16mm film; Aprroximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Auburn (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Auburn (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 8 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 7) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 7) [labeled on canister as Tiger], 22 Oct. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 12 Nov. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense, black & white duplicate], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense, black & white duplicate], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes, 45 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense, black & white duplicate], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense, black & white duplicate], 3 Sept. 1977 (Carton 29)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 5 minutes, 45 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Iowa State (Peach Bowl) (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 31 Dec. 1977 (Carton 29)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 12 minutes, 45 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Iowa State (Peach Bowl) (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 31 Dec. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Iowa State (Peach Bowl) (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 31 Dec. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Iowa State (Peach Bowl) (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 31 Dec. 1977 (Carton 29)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 17 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Iowa State (Peach Bowl) WRAL-TV broadcast materials, Dec. 1977 (Carton 29)
  Television broadcast film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute; color; sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st Half Defense], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 29)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st Qtr. 10-1-77], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 1 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 5 Nov. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 5 Nov. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 5 Nov. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 5 Nov. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 29 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Sept. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 30)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
  This film has been converted to digital beta (also stored in carton 31), and is also stored as an mp4 file from which copies can be reproduced
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 15 Oct. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 10 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 24 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 24 Sept. 1977 (Carton 31)